(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],[,,,,function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(13)},,,,,function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),l=n.n(a),r=n(3),o=n.n(r),i=(n(9),function(){return l.a.createElement("div",{className:"App-header"},l.a.createElement("h1",null,"Flashcardz!"),l.a.createElement("h5",null,"(AWS Cloud Practitioner Certification Training)"))}),c=n(1),s=[{id:1,question:"Which AWS service provides API monitoring and logging?",answer:"Cloud Trail"},{id:2,question:"Which AWS tool provides an IDE in the cloud?",answer:"Cloud9"},{id:3,question:"What service provides secure and resizable compute capacity?",answer:"EC2"},{id:4,question:"What enables on demand delivery of compute, database, applications, and other IT resources?",answer:"Cloud computing"},{id:5,question:"What are the 3 cloud based deployment models that AWS allows for?",answer:"public, private, and hybrid cloud"},{id:6,question:"What are the 3 types of cloud computing?",answer:"1. Infrastructure as a Service (IAAS) 2. Platform as a Service (PAAS) 3. Software as a Service (SAAS)"},{id:7,question:"What contains 84 Availability Zones within 26 geographic regions around the world, with announced plans for 24 more Availability Zones and 8 more AWS Regions in Australia, Canada, India, Israel, New Zealand, Spain, Switzerland, and United Arab Emirates (UAE).?",answer:"AWS Global Infrastructure"},{id:8,question:"What is a fully isolated partition of AWS infrastructure?",answer:"Availability Zone"},{id:9,question:"What is a global geographic location with AWS data centers called?",answer:"AWS region"},{id:10,question:"What is the name of a model where the customer assumes responsibility and management of the guest operating system (including updates and security patches), other associated application software as well as the configuration of the AWS provided security group firewall?",answer:"AWS shared responsibility model"}],u=(n(10),0),m=0,d=function(){var e=Object(a.useState)(0),t=Object(c.a)(e,2),n=t[0],r=t[1],o=Object(a.useState)(!1),i=Object(c.a)(o,2),d=i[0],h=i[1],b=Object(a.useState)(0),g=Object(c.a)(b,2),p=(g[0],g[1]);return l.a.createElement("div",{className:"main"},l.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-12",style:{textAlign:"right",marginRight:"2%"}},l.a.createElement("h5",null,l.a.createElement("bold",null,"Score: ",m)),l.a.createElement("br",null)),l.a.createElement("div",{className:"card"},l.a.createElement("div",{className:"card-body"},l.a.createElement("h5",{className:"card-title",style:{textAlign:"left"}},"Card# ",s[n].id),l.a.createElement("br",null),l.a.createElement("h6",{className:"card-subtitle mb-2 text-muted"},s[n].question),l.a.createElement("br",null),l.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){h(!0)}},"show"),l.a.createElement("br",null),l.a.createElement("br",null),!0===d?l.a.createElement("p",{className:"card-text"},s[n].answer):l.a.createElement("p",null))),l.a.createElement("br",null),l.a.createElement("div",{className:"button-div col-2"},l.a.createElement("button",{style:{marginBottom:"10%",marginRight:"30%"},type:"button",className:"btn btn-info",onClick:function(){if(h(!1),console.log("content length = ".concat(s.length)),-1===--u)return u++,void alert("You have reached the beginning!");r(u),console.log("newCount = ".concat(u))}},"Previous"),l.a.createElement("button",{style:{marginBottom:"10%"},type:"button",className:"btn btn-info",onClick:function(){if(h(!1),console.log("content length = ".concat(s.length)),++u===s.length)return u--,void alert("You have reached the end!");r(u),console.log("newCount = ".concat(u))}},"Next"),l.a.createElement("br",null),l.a.createElement("span",null,l.a.createElement("button",{style:{marginRight:"20%"},type:"button",className:"btn btn-success",onClick:function(){p(++m)}},"+"),l.a.createElement("button",{type:"button",className:"btn btn-danger",onClick:function(){-1!==--m?p(m):alert("Can't have a score of less than 0!")}},"-")),l.a.createElement("br",null),l.a.createElement("button",{style:{marginTop:"10%"},type:"button",className:"btn btn-warning",onClick:function(){m=0,h(!1),r(u=0),console.log("newCount reset")}},"Reset")))},h=(n(11),function(){return l.a.createElement("div",null,l.a.createElement("footer",{className:"page-footer font-small"},l.a.createElement("div",{className:"footer",style:{textAlign:"center"}},l.a.createElement("p",null,"Copyright 2022: Justin Sykes"))))});n(12);var b=function(){return l.a.createElement(l.a.Fragment,null,l.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},l.a.createElement(i,null),l.a.createElement("br",null),l.a.createElement("br",null),l.a.createElement(d,null),l.a.createElement(h,null)))},g=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&n.e(3).then(n.bind(null,14)).then(function(t){var n=t.getCLS,a=t.getFID,l=t.getFCP,r=t.getLCP,o=t.getTTFB;n(e),a(e),l(e),r(e),o(e)})};o.a.render(l.a.createElement(l.a.StrictMode,null,l.a.createElement(b,null)),document.getElementById("root")),g()}],[[4,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.2fcfb6ba.chunk.js.map